# Files in the config/locales directory are used for internationalization
# and are automatically loaded by Rails. If you want to use locales other
# than English, add the necessary files in this directory.
#
# To use the locales, use `I18n.t`:
#
#     I18n.t 'hello'
#
# In views, this is aliased to just `t`:
#
#     <%= t('hello') %>
#
# To use a different locale, set it with `I18n.locale`:
#
#     I18n.locale = :es
#
# This would use the information in config/locales/es.yml.
#
# To learn more, please read the Rails Internationalization guide
# available at http://guides.rubyonrails.org/i18n.html.

en:
  title: "Framgia Test"
  time_format: "%c"
  home: "Home"
  sign_up: "Sign up"
  sign_in: "Sign in"
  sign_out: "Sign out"
  log_in: "Log in"
  profile: "Profile"
  edit_something: "Edit %{name}"
  edit_profile: "Edit profile"
  welcome: "Welcome to Framgia Testing System"
  login_now: "Login now"
  footer: "Framgia Test"
  update_button: "Save changes"
  delete_account_button: "Delete account"
  back_button: "Back"
  delete_account_confirm: "Are you sure you want to delete this account? This action cannot be undone!"
  need_current_password: "(Require current password)"
  leave_password: "(leave blank if you don't want to change it)"
  waiting_confirm_for: "Currently waiting confirmation for: %{email}"
  reset_password_button: "Send me reset password instructions"
  forgot_password_title: "Forgot password"
  forgot_password: "Forgot your password?"
  contribute_questions: "Contribute questions"
  change_password_title: "Change password"
  change_password: "Change your password"
  new_password: "New password"
  confirm_new_password: "Confirm new password"
  change_my_password: "Change my password"
  form_error_messages: "The form contains %{plural}."
  error_text: "error"
  pictures:
    max_size_message: "Maximum file size is %{max_size}MB. Please choose a smaller file."
    error_message: "Image should be less than %{max_size}MB"
  flash:
    success:
      created_subject: "Created subject successfully!"
      destroy_user: "Delete user successfully!"
      deleted_subject: "Deleted subject successfully!"
      updated_subject: "Update subject successfully!"
      contributed_question: "Contributed question successfully!"
      created_question: "Create question successfully!"
      created_exam: "Create exam successfully!"
      deleted_question: "Deleted subject successfully!"
      saved_exam: "Saved exam successfully!"
      finished_exam: "Finished exam successfully!"
      updated_question: "Update subject successfully!"
      checked_exam: "Checked exam successfully!"
    danger:
      created_subject: "Created subject failed!"
      destroy_user: "Delete user failed!"
      deleted_subject: "Deleted subject failed!"
      updated_subject: "Update subject failed!"
      subject_not_found: "Subject is not found!"
      contributed_question: "Contributed question failed!"
      created_exam: "Create exam failed!"
      deleted_question: "Deleted subject failed!"
      exam_not_found: "Exam is not found!"
      saved_exam: "Saved exam failed!"
      finished_exam: "Finished exam failed!"
      updated_question: "Update subject failed!"
      checked_exam: "Checked exam failed!"
    notice:
      permission_denied: "You're not admin!"
  users:
    sign_up:
      min_characters: "(%{length} characters minimum)"
  admin:
    subjects:
      index:
        create_subject: "New Subject"
        title: "All subjects"
        edit: "Edit"
        delete: "Delete"
        delete_subject_confirm: "Are you sure you want to delete this subject? This action cannot be undone!"
        index: "Index"
        name: "Subject's Name"
        question_number: "Questions"
        duration: "Duration"
        actions: "Actions"
        delete: "Delete"
      new:
        create_subject: "Create Subject"
        cancel_button: "Cancel"
        create_button: "Create"
        save_button: "Save changes"
      edit:
        edit_subject: "Edit Subject"
        edit_button: "Create"
        save_button: "Save changes"
      form:
        cancel_button: "Cancel"
        no_image: "There is no image to be shown."
      show:
        question_type: "Type"
        action: "Action"
        create_by: "Create by"
        delete_button: "Delete"
        edit_button: "Edit"
        delete_question_confirm: "Do you want delet this question?"
        content: "Content"
    users:
      index: "Index"
      name: "Name"
      email: "Email"
      chatwork: "Chatwork"
      role: "Role"
      create_at: "Create at"
      acion: "Action"
      btn_view: "View"
      btn_edit: "Edit"
      btn_delete: "Delete"
      delete_user: "Are you sure you want to delete this user?"
      form:
        submit_button: "Save"
      update:
        update_success: "Update user successfully"
        update_fail: "Update user fail"
    questions:
      answer: "Answer"
      new:
        suggest_question: "Suggest Question"
        create_button: "Save"
      form:
        question_content: "Type question's content here..."
        add_answer: "Add answer"
        submit_button: "Suggest"
        question_content_error: "At least 5 characters"
      answer_fields:
        answer_content: "Type answer's content here..."
        remove_answer: "Remove"
        answer_content_error: "Answer must have content"
        answer: "Answer"
      index:
        suggested_questions: "Suggested Questions"
        delete_question_confirm: "Do you want delet this question?"
        new_question: "New question"
        question: "Question"
        subject_name: "Subject's name"
        answer_type: "Answer's type"
        status: "Status"
        content: "Content"
        create_by: "Create by"
        edit: "Edit"
      errors:
        must_more_one: "must has more than 1 answer"
        must_has_correct_answer: "must has at least 1 correct answer"
      questions:
        index:
          new_question: "New Question"
        new:
          create_button: "Save"
      edit:
        suggest_question: "Suggest Question"
        create_button: "Save"
    exams:
      questions:
        save: "Save"
        checked: "Checked"
      index:
        check_button: "Check"
        view_button: "View"
        created_date: "Created Date"
        subject_name: "Subject's name"
        status: "Status"
        duration: "Duration"
        question_number: "Question number"
        spent_time: "Spent Time"
        score: "Score"
        action: "Action"
        create_button: "Create Exam"
        exam_list: "Examination List"
        title: "Exams"
        user: "User"
  logs:
    admin_log: "Admin logs"
  questions:
    answer: "Answer"
    new:
      suggest_question: "Suggest Question"
    form:
      question_content: "Type question's content here..."
      add_answer: "Add answer"
      submit_button: "Suggest"
      question_content_error: "At least 5 characters"
    answer_fields:
      answer_content: "Type answer's content here..."
      remove_answer: "Remove"
      answer_content_error: "Answer must have content"
      answer: "Answer"
    index:
      suggested_questions: "Suggested Questions"
      new_question: "New question"
      question: "Question"
      subject_name: "Subject's name"
      answer_type: "Answer's type"
      status: "Status"
    errors:
      must_more_one: "must has more than 1 answer"
      must_has_correct_answer: "must has at least 1 correct answer"
  exams:
    timeout: "Timeout. The exam is finished. The result will be sent to you."
    exam_date: "Exam start at: %{date}"
    time_out: "Your exam is time out. We are going to submit your test automatically"
    index:
      start_button: "Start"
      view_button: "View"
      created_date: "Created Date"
      subject_name: "Subject's name"
      status: "Status"
      duration: "Duration"
      question_number: "Question number"
      spent_time: "Spent Time"
      score: "Score"
      action: "Action"
      create_button: "Create Exam"
      exam_list: "Examination List"
      title: "Exams"
    show:
      time_remain: "Time remain:"
      hour: "Hours"
      minute: "Minutes"
      second: "Seconds"
    questions:
      save: "Save"
      finish: "Finish"
      finish_confirm: "Are you sure you want to finish this exam? This action cannot be undone!"
    answers:
      content_answer: "Your answer"
      content_answer_holder: "Type your answer here..."
      content_answer_hint: "This is a text answer. Please type your answer to the above field."
  labels:
    status:
      exam:
        start: "start"
        testing: "testing"
        uncheck: "uncheck"
        checked: "checked"
        inactive: "inactive"
      exam_question:
        correct: "correct"
        incorrect: "incorrect"
  time_format: "%H:%M:%S"
  date_format: "%Y/%m/%d"
  datetime_format: "%Y-%m-%d %l:%M %p"
  user_mailer:
    notify_user_new_subject:
      subject: "New subject in FTS_66: \"%{subject}\""
      dear_user: "Hi %{username},"
      body: "I'd like to inform you that \"%{subject_name}\" is available in system."
      signature: "FTS_66 team."
